Guide to the Gerard Malanga Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 2006 acquisition, 1906-2005; 81.05; (102 boxes) + 2 art, 6 rolls, 4 broadside folders
  - "Prelude to International Velvet Debutante, 1966" (Box 66)
  - Untitled folders, undated (Box 66)
  - "1960s" poems, 1964-1969, undated (Box 66)
  - "From 'Prelude Captian,' 1956-66, by Gerard Malanga", circa 1966 (Box 66)
  - Poems, 1971, undated (Box 66)
  - "'The Two or Three Girls I Once Knew,' a Partial Mss (1969)", undated (Box 66)
  - "Poems (ca. 1965-66) Omitted from Chic Death (1971)", 1964-1966, undated (Box 66)
  - "Subversion of the Pastoral", undated; 2 (Box 66)
  - "Poems of a Precocious Youth by Gerard Malanga. Mss Notes Intro", 1966-1988, undated (Box 66)
  - "'Clockwork / Poems 1964-66,' by Gerard Malanga, 1st Copy", circa 1966 (Box 66)
  - "'Clockwork / Poems 1964-66,' by Gerard Malanga (2nd Copy)", undated (Box 66)
  - " Chic Death, Selections from the Book", 1971 (Box 66)
  - Untitled folder, undated (Box 66)
  - "Research / Subversion of the Pastoral", 1990-1993, undated (Box 66)
  - "The Things We Do for England", 1977-1983, undated (Box 66)
  - Poems, 1963-1975, undated (Box 66)
  - "'Photographing Poets & Writers,' Essay, Working Drafts", 2005 (Box 66)
  - "John Thaw, Actor, 1942-2002", 2003, undated (Box 66)
  - "John Thaw, Actor, Mss", 2002, undated (Box 66)
  - "Cartier Foundation", 1990-1999, undated (Box 66)
  - "Additional Research for Bosnia Poem", 1999, undated (Box 66)
  - "Paperwork Involving My Speaking Engagement in Nurnberg...", undated (Box 66)
  - "'For Julien's Photographs,' Notes & Drafts, 2000", 2000-2001 (Box 66)
  - "Episodic (Paris) G Poems", 2000 (Box 66)
  - "Stellan Holm Gallery", 2001, undated (Box 66)
  - "'Working with Warhol,' by Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 66)
  - "Akademie der Bildenden Kunste (Nurnberg, Germany) re: 'Brillo Box,' Text by Gerard Malanga", 1999-2000 (Box 66)
  - "'Archiving Warhol,' by Gerard Malanga / Creation Books Texts", undated (Box 66)
  - "Christophe van de Weghe Fine Art, November 2000 / 'The Kiss' Essay" (Box 66)
  - "Emma Lovetere, neé Malanga. Gerard's Mother", 1972-1997, undated (Box 66)
  - "Jedi, ca. 1991. Gerard's Best Friend, Younger Brother to Adam Weinberg, Director, Whitney Museum", circa 1991 (Box 66)
  - "Princeton University Residency Fellowship. Hodder Fellowship", 1984 November 3 (Box 66)
  - "Sasha Pabst: Fotos Relating to Gerard", 2004, undated (Box 66)
  - "Malanga Photography Exhibition Announcements", 2003-2006, undated (Box 66)
  - "Piero Heliczer Transcript of Interview w/ Marisabine Russo, Piero's Baby Sister, To Be Included in Piero's Collected Poetry, 'A Purchase in the White Botanica' (2001), Granary Books" (Box 66)
  - "'Who's There?' Working Drafts, 2004" (Box 66)
  - "Screen Test Redoux", 2003 (Box 66)
  - "'Voysey' - Working Drafts", 2003, undated; 2 (Box 66)
  - "'Shilling the Flick' - Drafts", 2003-2004 (Box 66)
  - "Filippo Tomasso Marinetti ora passato", undated (Box 66)
  - "Albin Krebs, Obit Writer - Drafts", 2003 (Box 66)
  - "'Sir Alex Korda,' Working Drafts, 2004" (Box 66)
  - "Fathers' Days", 2002 (Box 67)
  - "Sometimes Repeated", 2004 (Box 67)
  - "'The Hinged Mirror,' Tentative Title - 2004", 2004 April 11 (Box 67)
  - "John Chamberlain, Working Drafts, 2004" (Box 67)
  - "'Giorgio Morandi,' Poem, Working Drafts", 2005 (Box 67)
  - "'Nino Rota,' Working Drafts, 2004" (Box 67)
  - "An Unfinished Work (Title)", 2003 (Box 67)
  - "Orson Wells Dream, 5:iv:04", 2004 (Box 67)
  - "'The Corpse in the Green Pajamas,' Drafts, 2004" (Box 67)
  - "'Tyger Tyger Burning Bright...' Working Drafts, 2004" (Box 67)
  - "'The Milanese Twilight,' Working Drafts Starting 2:x:04", 2004 (Box 67)
  - "'Rosie,' Working Drafts - 1:xi:04", 2004 November 1 (Box 67)
  - "'Ted,' Working Drafts - 31:x:04", 2004 (Box 67)
  - "Thomas Hardy, Notes Towards a Poem, 2004" (Box 67)
  - "'Lost Light,' (Arshile) Working Drafts, 2004", 2004 April 4 (Box 67)
  - "'The Day Before April 13, 2004,' Working Drafts & Notes" (Box 67)
  - "'Paradise' (Tentative Title), Working Drafts, 2004" (Box 67)
  - "Sylvia Poem Drafts, 2004. Plus Ancillary Materials", 1990-2004, undated (Box 67)
  - "'The Bronx,' (1998) Working Drafts" (Box 67)
  - "A Falcon Nearby", 2003 (Box 67)
  - "'Federico Garcia-Lorca: His Student Days in New York", 2003 (Box 67)
  - "W. H. Auden Poem Drafts", 2001 (Box 67)
  - "Robert Lowell Poem Drafts", undated (Box 67)
  - "'3-minutes B&W Silent,' Started 25:vii:2000, Working Drafts" (Box 67)
  - Photographs, 1969-2005 (Box 68 (Oversize))
  - Photographs, 1969-1981 (Box 69 (Oversize))
  - Photographs, 1964-2002, undated (Box 70 (Oversize))
  - Photographs, 1970-2002, undated (Box 71 (Oversize))
  - Miscellaneous writings, 2003 (Box 72)
  - "'Anthony Hecht,' Notes for a Poem Starting 25:x:04", 2004 (Box 72)
  - "Celia Paget in an Undated Photo" (Box 72)
  - "Who Remembers George Barker?", 2003-2004 (Box 72)
  - "Rip van Winkle - 2 Versions", 2002-2004 (Box 72)
  - Miscellaneous writings, 2003-2004; 2 (Box 72)
  - "Fugitive or Abandoned Poems", 2002-2003 (Box 72)
  - "'Baron Haussmann Sweeps Through Paris,' Working Drafts Starting I:2000" (Box 72)
  - "Notes for a Poem", 2004 May (Box 72)
  - "'Autumn Days,' Working Drafts, 9:viii:04", 2004, undated (Box 72)
  - "'Paul Rotha,' Working Drafts, 2004", 2004 July (Box 72)
  - "'Umberto Boccioni,' Draft Notes, 2004" (Box 72)
  - "Telegraph Wires (Tentative Title), Draft Notes, 2004" (Box 72)
  - "'America as Seen from Outer Space,' Drafts, 2004" (Box 72)
  - "'The Harold Interlocking,' Working Drafts, 2004" (Box 72)
  - "'Blanchot,' Working Notes, 2004" (Box 72)
  - "'Radio Wavelengths,' Working Drafts, 2004" (Box 72)
  - "'The Sheltering Palms,' Working Drafts, 2004", 2003-2004 (Box 72)
  - "'Other,' Working Drafts, 2004" (Box 72)
  - Envelope, undated (Box 72)
  - Charles Henri Ford Arena Books project, 2000-2003, undated; 4 (Box 72)
  - I Will Be What I Am by Charles Henri Ford, undated; 3 (Box 72)
  - Charles Henri Ford Arena Books project, undated; 6 (Box 72)
  - Charles Henri Ford GM's Set, 2002, undated; 5 (Box 73)
  - Charles Henri Ford Arena Editions, undated; 5 (Box 73)
  - "Jim Jacobs - Artwork. Framed Feathers", undated (Box 73)
  - "48 Cameras & Gerard Malanga", 1999; 1 (Box 73)
  - "Notes on Marie Menka", undated; 1 (Box 73)
  - Printed materials, 2005-2006, undated; 4 (Box 73)
  - "Dental Records 2002 - 2004", 2002-2004, undated; 3 (Box 73)
  - Viennale box, 2005 (Box 73)
  - Viennale box 2005, 2005, undated (Box 74)
  - "Gerard's Exhibit - Vienna in Conjunction w/ Viennale", 2005, undated (Box 74)
  - "Asako's T-Shirt Commission Viennale", 2005 (Box 74)
  - "Gerard Malanga's Film Notebooks. World Premeire: 2005 Viennale", 2005, undated (Box 74)
  - "Aram Saroyan's Text for Gerard's Movies at the 2005 Viennale" (Box 74)
  - "Press Release / Filmography", 2005, undated (Box 74)
  - "Martina Kudlacek / Interview with Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 74)
  - "Martina Kudlacek 'Notes on Marie Menken'", 2002-2005, undated (Box 74)
  - "Opening Remarks: The Viennale 2005. Working Drafts", 2005, undated (Box 74)
  - "Viennale 2005", 2005, undated; 2 (Box 74)
  - "Viennale 2005 Press Materials & Programmes", 2005, undated; 2 (Box 74)
  - Viennale box 2005, 2004 October 10 (Box 74)
  - Correspondence, 1997-2006; 8 (Box 74)
  - "Transcribed Interview, Asako Kitaori", 1997, undated (Box 74)
  - "Asako Interview Charles Henri Ford, 5/23/97 Transcribed / Copy-edited by Gerard", undated (Box 74)
  - "Gerard Malanga: Interview by Asako Kitaori, 25-26:i:97", 1997; 2 (Box 74)
  - "Asako Interviews Taylor Mead, 1/20/97", 1997; 2 (Box 75)
  - "Louis Waldon: Interview by Asako Kitaori, March 18, 1997, Los Angeles", 1997, undated; 2 (Box 75)
  - Drafts of poetry, 2003, undated; 3 (Box 75)
  - "Maurice Fall 1950. Draft Notes, 2005" (Box 75)
  - "Pre-posthumous for Benedetta Barzini. Working Drafts and Research Tearsheets.", 2005, undated (Box 75)
  - "Django Rheinhardt Working Drafts, 2005", 2005, undated (Box 75)
  - "Bill Brandt, First Draft Notes, 2005", 2005, undated (Box 75)
  - "1922, Working Drafts. 2005", 2005, undated (Box 75)
  - "'Mimmo Rotella, 1918-2006,' Working Drafts", 2006, undated (Box 75)
  - "Jackson Pollock Notes, 5/29/05", 2005-2006, undated (Box 75)
  - "The Hinged Mirror, for Marcel Duchamp", 2005, undated (Box 75)
  - "Brion Gysin", undated (Box 75)
  - "3 Versions of Marie Menken Poem", 2005, undated (Box 75)
  - "Photographing Edward Morin", 2005, undated (Box 75)
  - "'Dr. Paul de Kloci, Marine Painter,' Working Drafts, 2004", 2004, undated (Box 75)
  - "Notes for a Poem, 30:IV:05", 2005 (Box 75)
  - "Macchina la Scrivere 1st Written Notes, 2005", 2005 February (Box 75)
  - "Mario Schifano Perfetto 1934-1998, Working Drafts", 2005 (Box 75)
  - "Luciano Erba - Working Drafts", 2005 (Box 75)
  - "Belgian Skies - Drafts", undated (Box 75)
  - "John Frederick Kensett, Working Drafts, 2005", 2005, undated (Box 75)
  - "Another Derrida, Working Drafts - 1:XI:04", 2004, undated (Box 75)
  - "Derrida Poem / Notes, 2004", 2004, undated (Box 75)
  - "Working Drafts - Related Material", 2003-2004, undated (Box 75)
  - "Assorted E-mails", 2001-2005, undated (Box 75)
  - "Pertinent E-mails / Invoices etc. / Poem Draft", 1999-2002 (Box 75)
  - "S.R. Lavin, Founder Four Zoas Press", 2006, undated (Box 75)
  - "Gianni Penati, Italian Photographer", 2001, undated (Box 75)
  - "Tsuyoshi Kawose, Examples of His Silkscreen Work", undated (Box 75)
  - "Pamela Anderson Catalogue by Sante D'Orazio", undated (Box 75)
  - "'Eyes Are the Windows to the Soul' Asako, Portraits 1995-1996. Working Drafts", 1995-1996, undated (Box 75)
  - "'Charles Olson Is Dead' by Gerard Malanga. Original Facsimile Typescript w/ Revisions", undated (Box 75)
  - The American Poetry Review - fax, 2002 August 21 (Box 75)
  - "Salvador Dali", undated (Box 75)
  - "Swimming-pool Text to Exhibit", undated (Box 75)
  - "Alajos Schuszler, Phantom Photographer", undated (Box 75)
  - "Tsuyoshi Kawasoe File", 2000-2002, undated (Box 75)
  - Tsuyoshi Kawasoe photographic print, undated (Box 75)
  - "Mark Francis: 'Andy Warhol & Fashion' Exhibit", 1998, undated (Box 75)
  - "Willard Maas", undated (Box 75)
  - "'The Arcades Project, Unfinished' Poem by Gerard Malanga, Published by Altaquito-Publikationen, Gotlingen", 2002-2003, undated (Box 76)
  - "Chain Magazine", 1999, undated (Box 76)
  - "Edwin Denby", 1955 (Box 76)
  - "Gerard Malanga on Isabel Garcia-Lorca de los Rios", undated (Box 76)
  - "Gerard Malanga 'Sacred Ground'", 1982 (Box 76)
  - "David Rattray", undated (Box 76)
  - "Piero Heliczer", undated (Box 76)
  - "Ted Berrigan", undated (Box 76)
  - "Ira Cohen", undated (Box 76)
  - "Drafts to Memoir Project", undated (Box 76)
  - "Regis Cotentin / Caen, France", 1995-2000, undated (Box 76)
  - "Martin Weinstein Gallery", 2000, undated (Box 76)
  - "One-of-a-Kind Broadside Typescript of Poem to Paul Blackburn", 1998 (Box 76)
  - "Archival Girls, Draft", undated (Box 76)
  - "Naked Eye. Simon Dwyer, Editor", 1989-1990, undated (Box 76)
  - "C.C. Chan, Hong Kong", 1998, undated (Box 76)
  - "Original Typescripts + Drafts, Signed", 1974-1993, undated; 2 (Box 76)
  - "Peter Barton", 2004-2005; (1 folder, 1 compact disc) (Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous material, 2003, undated (Box 76)
  - "Robert Creeley: Recollections. Drafts & Research", 1999-2005, undated; 2 (Box 76)
  - "Daido Moriyama Essay / Catalogue Raisonne", 2003-2004, undated; 2 (Box 76)
  - "Daido Moriyama", 2000-2004, undated (Box 76)
  - "Fahey - Klein", 2002-2003, undated (Box 76)
  - "'Archeology of the Thermofax,' Essay by Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 76)
  - "Judith Keller / The Getty", 1997-1999 (Box 76)
  - "'Gerard Malanga Speaking,' Text - March 28, 1987 for V.V.", 1987 March 28 (Box 76)
  - "W. H. Auden, Memoir", undated (Box 76)
  - "Dominique Gelle / Editions en vues", 1997-1998 (Box 76)
  - "Maison de la poesie - Paris. Reading Engagement, March 10, 2001", 2000-2001 (Box 76)
  - "Centre Pompidou - 2001 Colloque Paperwork & Associated Documents", 1997-2001 (Box 76)
  - "Reimbursements / Centre Pompidou", 2000 (Box 76)
  - "Official Press Kits for 'Les années Pop' - Centre Pompidou", undated (Box 76)
  - "Correspondence Received During Gerard & Asako's Visit to Paris Sponsored by Centre Pompidou", 2001, undated (Box 76)
  - "Correspondence and Related Documents for Les années Pop Exhibit, Centre Georges Pompidou, Paris, 2001", 2000-2005; 2 (Box 77)
  - "Press: 'Les années Pop,' Centre Pompidou", 2000-2001, undated; 2 (Box 77)
  - "Centre Pompidou Exhibition Announcements", 1997-2001 (Box 77)
  - "Jean-Michel Bouhours, Curator of Film, Centre Pompidou. Additional Correspondence", 2000-2001 (Box 77)
  - "Michel Bulteau Interviews...", 2000, undated (Box 77)
  - "Loans Documentation for 'Les années Pop' Exhibit Centre Georges Pompidou, Paris, 2001", 2000-2001 (Box 77)
  - "Steidl / Photocopy Proofs", 1998-1999 (Box 77)
  - "Edgar Morin, Philosopher", 2001 (Box 77)
  - "Museo la triennale, Milano, Malanga Checklist", circa 2004 (Box 77)
  - "Gerard Malanga's Poetry Reading Performance at Carla Sozzani Gallery, 2004" (Box 77)
  - "Mailing List for Gerard Malanga's Exhibition, 'Then and Now,' at the Carla Sozzani Gallery, Milano, 2004" (Box 77)
  - "Icons of Photography. Publisher: Taschen. This Edition Includes a Chapter on Gerard Malanga's Photographs of The Velvet Underground", 2000-2002 (Box 77)
  - "Galleria Carla Sozzani Industrial Space. Malanga Sampler", 2004 (Box 77)
  - "'Factory Girl,' Filmscript Inscribed by Guy Pearce, Who Portrays Warhol in the Movie, 2005", 2005 November 4 (Box 77)
  - "Gerard Malanga / Gianfranco Farioli Press Kit", 2005 (Box 77)
  - "Gerard Malanga / Gianfranco Farioli Collaboration, Milano, 2005" (Box 77)
  - "Press Release Particuleurs to the FNAC Travelling Exhibition for Gerard Malanga's Photographs, Photographs & Screen Tests 1964-1995. Exhibition Schedule: 1998", 1998-2006 (Box 77)
  - " Factory Girl, 2 Drafts of the Screenplay for the Movie About the Life of Edie Sedgwick in Which Gerard Malanga's Character Is Portrayed by Jack Huston. Release Date: Fall 2006", 2004-2005; 2 (Box 77)
  - "Pierre-Paul Puljiz, Producer, Paris: Andy Warhol TV Programme, 2006", (1 folder, 1 DVD) (Box 78)
  - "Charles Plymell, Poet, Correspondence", 2001-2005 (Box 78)
  - "Angus MacLise / The Cooler, 2001" (Box 78)
  - "Akio Mokuno, Experimental Composer", 2001 (Box 78)
  - "Photo Inquiries", 2001 March 5 (Box 78)
  - "Illustration Based on a Photo of the Velvet Underground by Gerard Malanga", undated (Box 78)
  - "John Martin / Black Sparrow Press", 1995-2003 (Box 78)
  - The Virgin of Bennington by Kathleen Norris, typescript, 2000; 2 (Box 78)
  - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 78)
  - "Comune di Roma Group Exhibition", 2001 (Box 78)
  - "'The Whole Warhol,' UK TV Documentary", 2001-2002 (Box 78)
  - "Fernanda Pivano on Gerard Malanga", 2004-2005 (Box 78)
  - "University of California Press. Unauthorized Use of Malanga Photograph", 2001-2002 (Box 78)
  - "Robert Frank", 1998 August 7 (Box 78)
  - "Acquisition of 'Screen Test' Prints / Tokyo", undated (Box 78)
  - "Art Gallery of Western Australia. Warhol Exhibit / License of Malanga Foto", 1999 (Box 78)
  - "Jean Marie Mathoul, Electronic Composer", 1999 (Box 78)
  - "Literary Imagination Mag", 2000-2001 (Box 78)
  - "Walker Art Center", 2002 (Box 78)
  - " Artforum ...", 1999 (Box 78)
  - "Photocopies / Selections from Chic Death ", undated (Box 78)
  - "Research into Defrauding the Life Savings of Emma Lovetere - Gerard Malanga's Mother", undated (Box 78)
  - "Active Files: Email Project Queries ca. Late '90s/Early 2000", 2000-2001, undated (Box 78)
  - "Warren Sonbert, Filmmaker", 2000 October (Box 78)
  - "Granary Books", 2000-2001 (Box 78)
  - "Re: Andy Warhol / Galerie F. Zeitgen Kunst Leipzig", 2002 (Box 78)
  - "David R. Godine, Publisher", 2002 July 11 (Box 78)
  - " On the Road Scroll Foto-inquiry", 2001 (Box 78)
  - "Grant Application: Lita Hornick Sponsor", 1988, 1995 (Box 78)
  - "Robert Bly Fotos-inquiry, 2001 (Box 78)
  - "Philip Conway, Atty", 1998-1999; 2 (Box 78)
  - "Joe Gallant, Rock Musician", circa 1995-1999 (Box 78)
  - "The Texas Gallery", 1999-2000 (Box 78)
  - "Jules Buis - in Preparation for Visit from Milan Itinerary, 2004" (Box 78)
  - "Bardo Pond - Music Group", 1997 (Box 78)
  - "4 Mona Lisas - Warhol... and Research", 2000-2001 (Box 78)
  - "Magazine Acceptances", 2003-2005; 2 (Box 78)
  - "Rejects", 2000 (Box 79)
  - "Magazine Rejects", 2001-2006; 5 (Box 79)
  - "N.E.A. Poetry" material, 1996-2004; 6 (Box 79)
  - "John Simon Guggenheim Fellowship" material, 2002-2004, undated; 2 (Box 79)
  - "For Your Consideration. Academy of American Poets. Subject: Annual Academy Fellowship 2001. Re: Publication of No Respect: New & Selected Poems 1964-2000", 2001, undated; 2 (Box 79)
  - "Jean-Jacques Lebel, Multimedia Artist", 1964-2002, undated; 2 (Box 79)
  - "Coded Photocopies of Illustrations for the Survey of Gerard Malanga's Work", undated; 3 (Box 79)
  - "Flow Chart & Receipt of Manuscripts", 1990, undated (Box 80)
  - Clippings, 1994, undated (Box 80)
  - "Photocopies of the Original Photographs", 1990 March 1 (Box 80)
  - "Robert Creeley: Overview A-1", 1990 (Box 80)
  - "#1 Opening Quote / Red Bass", undated (Box 80)
  - "#2 Tad Mann / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#3 Daisy Aldan / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#4 Gerard Malanga 'Letter to You in Nice' / Red Bass File", 1960 (Box 80)
  - "#5 Paul Katz / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#6 'In Memory of the T/N Conte Biancamano' / Red Bass File", 1969, undated (Box 80)
  - "#6A Timothy Baum / Typesetter File. + Malanga Appropriation Poem", undated (Box 80)
  - "#7 David Bourdon / Red Bass File", 1989, undated (Box 80)
  - "#8 'Whereabouts Unknown' / Red Bass File", 1976 (Box 80)
  - "#9 Victor Bockris / Red Bass File", 1989 (Box 80)
  - "#10 Mick Jagger Poem / Red Bass File", 1970 (Box 80)
  - "#11 Reva Wolf / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#12 'Chanel' / Red Bass FIle", undated (Box 80)
  - "#13 Aram Saroyan / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#14 Excerpts from The Secret Diaries / Red Bass File", 1966 (Box 80)
  - "#15 Ira Cohen / Red Bass FIle", 1989 (Box 80)
  - "#16 'Oggi' / Red Bass FIle", 1967 (Box 80)
  - "#17 Gregg Barrios / Red Bass File", 1967 (Box 80)
  - "#18 Excerpts from The Rome Diaries / Red Bass FIle", 1967 (Box 80)
  - "#19 Donnatella Manganotti / Red Bass File", 1968 (Box 80)
  - "#20 'Lavorare Stanca' / Red Bass File", 1980 (Box 80)
  - "#21 Gil Williams / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#22 'Society Make Up' / Red Bass File", 1970 (Box 80)
  - "#23 Hassni / Red Bass File", 1989 (Box 80)
  - "#24 'He Went Out Quietly' / Red Bass File", 1975 (Box 80)
  - "#25 Peter Wehrli / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#26 'The Aesthetics of Statistics' / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#27 Jim Jacobs / Red Bass File", 1989 (Box 80)
  - "#28 'The Journey' / Red Bass File", 1973 (Box 80)
  - "#29 William Terry Ork / Red Bass File", 1989 (Box 80)
  - "#30 '14 Lines to Make up the Sonnet Dead Romance' / Red Bass File", 1970 (Box 80)
  - "#31 Kathleen Norris / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#32 'Blueprint for Beauty' / Red Bass File", 1986 (Box 80)
  - "#33 Gerald Hausman / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#34 'Remembering the Berkshires' / Red Bass File", 1976 (Box 80)
  - "#35 Julia Friar / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#36 'Four One Seventy Four' / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#37 John Wieners / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#38 'To a Visionary Poet' / Red Bass File", 1971 (Box 80)
  - "#39 Sara Vogeler / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#40 'Eban' / Red Bass File", 1976 (Box 80)
  - "#41 Lita Hornick / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#42 Ted Berrigan Screen Test Sonnet / Red Bass File", 1966 (Box 80)
  - "#43 S. R. Lavin / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#44 'A Version of Dino Campana' / Red Bass File", 1968 (Box 80)
  - "#45 Dale Davis / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#46 'Andrea Bankoff, From a Letter' / Red Bass File", 1981 (Box 80)
  - "#47 Peter Delano / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#48 'Poem Paid for w/ a Dream-up NEA Grant' / Red Bass File", 1980 (Box 80)
  - "#49 Kevin Jeffrey Clarke / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#50 'Days of 1967' / Red Bass File" (Box 80)
  - "#51 Jim Condon / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#52 'Endangered Species' / Red Bass FIle", undated (Box 80)
  - "#53 Robert Diamond / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#54 'Appropriating Alajos Schuszler' / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#55 David Rattray / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#56 'Art Project: Mystery Woman' / Red Bass, 1983 (Box 80)
  - "#57 A.D. Coleman / Red Bass File", 1989 (Box 80)
  - "#58 '7:44 Amtrak' / Red Bass File", 1981 (Box 80)
  - "#59 Ben Maddow / Red Bass File", 1989 (Box 80)
  - "#60 'Ben Maddow Speaks' / Red Bass File", 1989 (Box 80)
  - "#61 Sarah Greenleaf Whittier / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#62 'Forty-One Line Poem' / Red Bass File", 1980 (Box 80)
  - "#63 Charles Giuliano / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#64 Some Things to Remember about Tri-X Poem by Gerard Malanga", 1993 (Box 80)
  - "#65 Joseph Coplan / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#66 Excerpt: Robert Moses: Photos From an Irretrievable Past by G. Malanga / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#67 Bernadette Mayer / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#68 Charles Henri Ford / Red Bass File", undated (Box 80)
  - "#69 Closing Quote / Red Bass", undated (Box 80)
  - "Manassas Review", 1981 March (Box 80)
  - Printed material, circa 1984-2004; 6 (Box 80)
  - Printed material, circa 1984-2004; 9 (Box 81)
  - "This Is Charles Olson Speaking" by Gerard Malanga, undated (Box 81)
  - Miscellaneous material, undated (Box 81)
  - "S. A. W. Originals", 1986 (Box 81)
  - "Original Mss for Photography Forum", undated (Box 81)
  - "Contributors' Notes", undated (Box 81)
  - "Gerard Malanga / Editorial Text", 1986 (Box 81)
  - "Gerard Malanga / Alajos Schuszler", undated (Box 81)
  - "Alajos Schuszler: Kidz, a Portfolio", undated (Box 81)
  - "Vincent Vallarino / Paul Strand", 1986 (Box 81)
  - "Dale Davis / Gerard Malanga" (empty), undated (Box 81)
  - "Aram Saroyan", undated (Box 81)
  - "Gerard Malanga / Jeff Day", undated (Box 81)
  - "S. R. Lavin", undated (Box 81)
  - "A. D. Coleman / Chris Enos", undated (Box 81)
  - "David Rattray", undated (Box 81)
  - "Gail Donnenfeld", undated (Box 81)
  - "Hank O'Neal / Liza Stelle", undated (Box 81)
  - "Ralph Gibson / Ralph Gibson", undated (Box 81)
  - "Chris Peditto / Paul Grillo", undated (Box 81)
  - "Timothy Baum / André Kertesz", undated (Box 81)
  - "Samples for the Format of the Paper Publication", 1986 (Box 81)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 81)
  - Printed material, 1990-2004 (Box 82 (Oversize))
  - Sketchbook, undated (Box 83 (Oversize))
  - Photographs, undated (Box 84 (Oversize))
  - Photographs, undated (Box 85 (Oversize))
  - Photographs, undated (Box 86 (Oversize))
  - "This Is the Send-off Plaque Put Together for Gerard's...", 1988 (Box 87 (Oversize))
  - Photovoyeurism envelopes, undated; 5 (Box 87 (Oversize))
  - "Photographs of Myrtle Ave & the Greenpoint Environs...", undated (Box 88 (Oversize))
  - "S. R. Lavin", undated (Box 88 (Oversize))
  - "Uma Thurman's Breasts", undated (Box 88 (Oversize))
  - Printed material, undated; 3 (Box 88 (Oversize))
  - "2nd & 3rd Copies of 'Pictures,' Delineated Photocopies by GM", undated (Box 89 (Oversize))
  - "2nd Draft Delineations of GM's 'Pictures'", undated (Box 89 (Oversize))
  - "Photographers: Lee Black Childers, Julia Murphy", undated (Box 89 (Oversize))
  - "Absolutely Archival", undated; 7 (Box 90 (Oversize))
  - "'Three Diamonds,' Color Stats Cover Samples", undated (Box 91 (Oversize))